kittens-pictures.com 2019-04-29

# Kittens New Tab

Last Modified: February 22, 2019

This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) governs the manner in which we process information collected from our users (" **you** ", " **your** " or " **user** ") in connection with the access to or use of our browser extensions, and the Services, all as detailed and defined in our End User License Agreement. We highly recommend you to read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to installing accessing or using our Product. 

This Privacy Policy is a part of the Company's End User License Agreement (“ **EULA** ” and collectively the “ **Terms** ”). Definitions herein shall have the same meaning as defined in the EULA.

We have included below information about which data is collected, how we process and use your data, but before we would like to explain the lawful basis on which we do so: (i) Where you sign up for any of our Services, we process your personal data in order to perform our contract with you; (ii) If we have a legitimate interest in processing data, such as online identifiers for operation purposes; (iii) We will also process your personal data where you have provided us with consent to do so. 

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, the last and updated version is reflected in the "Last Modified" heading above. In the event of a material change, we will make best efforts to provide a written notification. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: info@kittens-pictures.com (or as described below) 

## DATA COLLECTED AND PURPOSE OF USE

Depending on your interaction with us or our Services, we may collect two types of data from you: Non-identifiable information, which is made available or processed through your use of the Service, to clarify, this information does not disclose your identity (“ **Non-Personal Data** ”). The Non Personal Information includes technical information transmitted by your device including the type of operating system, device type, default browser; your aggregated use of the Services; usage statistics; language and the time stamp and approximate geographical location. We use this data solely to provide and enhance our Services and to enable their operation. Individually identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual (“ **Personal Data** ”), this information includes: (i) online identifiers such as IP addresses which we will use for the purpose of operating and customizing our Services; enhancing your experience, and; auditing and tracking usage statistics and traffic flow, detecting fraud, security or technical issues in connection with the Service; (ii) Search queries and browsing history which we will use for the purpose of offering relevant advertising based on the users’ searches; (iii) contact details (if voluntarily provided by you), which we will use solely for the purpose of providing you with the support you have requested or respond to your inquiry. We will process the contact history in order to improve our services, as well as resolve disputes. If we combine Personal Data with Non-Personal Data, the combined data will be treated as Personal Data. 

## SHARING DATA WITH THIRD PARTIES

Company will not share any Personal Data collected from you, except as follows and solely if applicable: (i) we may disclose or share Online Identifiers collected by us (as detailed above), for the purpose of operating our business and providing the Services, as well as to calculate payments and detect fraud, security or technical issues in connection with the Services; (ii) we may disclose your Personal Data to third parties when you consent to a particular disclosure. Please note that once you provide such consent, your information and its use shall be subject to other third party’s privacy practices and terms; (iii) we will share your Personal Data, solely to the extent needed to comply with any applicable law or permitted by it, regulation, legal process or governmental request (e.g., pursuant to law enforcement inquiries, subpoenas or court orders), or when we believe, in good faith, it is required in order to enforce our policies; (iv) we may share Personal Data, in the event of a corporate transaction (e.g. sale of a substantial part of our business, merger, consolidation or asset sale), as well as with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control. In such event, our affiliated companies or acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy; (v) we may disclose Personal Data to our service providers to perform requested services on our behalf, e.g. server provider, etc. In addition, third parties’ products (e.g., search feed providers) might be offered as part of the Service. Additional information regarding search feed provider privacy policy and opt-out of data collection is available [here](https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/products/searchservices/index.html) and [here](https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/).

## COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES

Company and its service providers use certain cookies and other technologies (e.g. web beacons, pixels, user agent, etc.), when you use the Services. Cookies are small pieces of information that is assigned to your device. Cookies can be used for various different purposes, such as: costume and improve the services, enabling you to navigate between pages efficiently, enable automatic activation of certain features, etc. You can find more information about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

We gather some information automatically, such as your usage data, by ourselves or by using third party service and store it in log files, as follows: (i) We use cookie knows as APPSESSID solely for functionality purposes; (ii) Our third party partners may use cookies when you use their services through our Services. 

Opt-Out: You may use your device or browser’s settings to disable some cookies. Please note that, if you choose to disable cookies, some features of our Services who rely upon the use of cookies, may not operate properly. Please refer to the support page of the browser you are using. In this regard, following are some links which you may find useful: [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) ; [FireFox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) ; [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) ; [Safari](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265) ; [Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4027947/windows-delete-cookies); [Opera](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)

## DATA SECURITY

Your privacy is very important to us and we are committed to protecting your information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We have implemented certain physical, technical and administrative security measures for the Services that comply with applicable laws and industry standards. Company pursues the minimization regarding the amount of data that it stores on its servers. If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our Privacy Policy, or if any person attempted gain unauthorized access to the Personal Data please contact us at: info@kittens-pictures.com. Further, in the event of a data incident, in which we discover your Personal Data may be at risk, then we will take reasonable efforts to notify you and the applicable authority (if required, subject to applicable laws). 

## LINKS TO THIRD PARTY CONTENT

Our Services may link to third party content whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Please note that we provide these features only as a suggestion. We are not, and will not be held responsible to privacy practices established by third party providers, thus, we encourage you to carefully read the privacy policies and terms of use of those third parties. 

## DATA RETENTION

We retain the data we have collected for as long as needed to provide the Service, carry out our business purpose and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements, in accordance and compliance with applicable laws, or until an individual request us to delete its Personal Data, as detailed below. 

## USER RIGHTS

Individuals have the right to know what information we hold about them and, in some cases, to have such information communicated to them. Individuals may also ask for our confirmation as to whether or not we process their Personal Data. Subject to the limitations in applicable law, individuals may also be entitled to obtain from us the Personal Data they have provided to us in a structured, commonly-used, and machine-readable format, and may have the right to transmit such Personal Data to another party. The principal rights under applicable data protection law in relation to Personal Data are as follows: the right to access any information which is provided to us; the right to rectification; the right to erasure; the right to restrict processing; the right to object to processing; the right to data portability; the right to complain to a supervisory authority; and the right to withdraw consent (to the extent applicable).  
If you wish to exercise any or all of the above rights, please download our applicable form available here and send it to our privacy team at: info@kittens-pictures.com  
Where we are not able to provide you with the information for which you have asked, we will endeavor to explain the reasoning for this and inform you of your rights, including the right to complain to the supervisor authority. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any such information in accordance with applicable law. In addition, the process of locating and deleting the data may take up to one (1) month (following the receipt of the validation proof we require) in accordance with applicable law. Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply. 

Where we are not able to provide you with the information for which you have asked, we will endeavor to explain the reasoning for this and inform you of your rights, including the right to complain to the supervisor authority. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any such information in accordance with applicable law. In addition, the process of locating and deleting the data may take up to one (1) month (following the receipt of the validation proof we require) in accordance with applicable law.  
Data privacy and related laws in your jurisdiction may provide you with different or additional rights related to the data we collect from you, which may also apply. 

## DATA TRANSFER 

We may store or process your Personal Data in the EEA, United States or in other countries. If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (" **EEA** ") we will take appropriate measures to ensure that your Personal Data receives an adequate level of data protection upon its transfer outside of the EEA. If you are a resident of a jurisdiction, where transfer of your Personal Data requires your consent, then your consent to this Privacy Policy includes your express consent for such transfer of your data. 

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Services are not intended for children, accordingly, we do not use the Service to knowingly solicit data from children as defined under applicable law (e.g. thirteen (13) regarding US individuals and sixteen (16) regarding European Economic Area (" **EEA** ") individuals) (collectively “ **Child** ”). We request that Children do not provide Personal Data through our Services. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a child has shared any information with us, please contact us at: info@kittens-pictures.com and we take reasonable steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our files. 

## DO NOT TRACK DISCLOSURE

The Product does not respond to Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track signals, please see: [http://www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

## CONTACT US

If you have any general questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact us, as follows:

info@kittens-pictures.com
